{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622782","name":"Fast Treats","address":"6211 W Warren Ave","zipcode":"4821","owner":"Ali Sobh","licenseNumber":"PS061818","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.12931,42.34430","geojson":{"id":"51622782","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.129309833,42.344304891]},"properties":{"name":"Fast Treats","owner":"Ali Sobh","address":"6211 W Warren Ave","zipcode":"4821","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"PS061818","establishmentid":"51622782","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1794","name":"White Castle #18","address":"6301 W Warren Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"1275","name":"Munger PK-8","address":"5525 Martin","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"51622883","name":"El Molcajete","address":"4930 Livernois","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"5090","name":"Subway","address":"4930 Livernois","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"5089","name":"La Zacatecana","address":"4930 Livernois","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3481","name":"Matrix Head Start","address":"5690 Cecil","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"1278","name":"Onasis Coney Island ","address":"8001 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"1389","name":"Tabernacle Missionary Baptist Church","address":"6125 Beechwood St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"2023","name":"La Sierra","address":"5400 Chopin","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"51622564","name":"La Nueva Sierra","address":"5400 Chopin St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"5426","name":"Asty Time Inc.","address":"7340 McGraw Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","address":"5546 McGraw St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"655","name":"PVT Kozdron Memorial  Home Assoc.","address":"2501 N Campell St","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"660","name":"Telway System","address":"6820 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"1013","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #302","address":"7060 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1375","name":"McDonald's #7453","address":"6876 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"716","name":"Jordans Family Restaurant","address":"7031 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"2073","name":"Senor Lopez Taqueria Mexican","address":"7146 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3914","name":"Subway #29822","address":"7300 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"950","name":"Kwong Village Chinese American","address":"6600 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43833","inspectionDate":"2018-10-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"43777","inspectionDate":"2018-10-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45156","inspectionDate":"2018-10-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45230","inspectionDate":"2018-07-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelves","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"and the Cold holding equipment","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the Back Room","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the Back Room","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"From contamination","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"},{"violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not frozen solid","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelves","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain frozen."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"doors","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Door handles","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622782"}}